<schedule date="5/12/2015">
    <breakfast>
        <recipe name = "Tacos" type = "Main Course" prep = "30 Minutes">
            <description>A decadent flour based eating utility stuffed with delicious meats and vegetables of beaner origin.</description>
            <ingredient amount = "1 pound">Ground Beef</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1 cup">Water</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1/4 cup">Taco seasoning mix</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "Hella">Hard or Soft taco shells</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "One">Onion</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "Two">Tomato</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "A handful">Cilantro</ingredient>
            <step>Cook the ground beef until completely brown, and drain the fat.</step>
            <step>Next, add 1 cup water and 1/4 cup taco seasoning mix, and stir until combined. Leave on heat to evaporate the water.</step>
            <step>While the water is boiling off of the meat, go ahead and chop up the two tomatoes, the onion, a the handful of cilantro </step>
        </recipe>
    </breakfast>
    <lunch>
        <recipe name = "Chicken Enchiladas" type = "Main Course" prep = "45 Minutes">
            <description>A great way to use leftover chicken. Even kids love these!</description>
            <ingredient amount = "1 Tablespoon">Butter</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1 Cup">Green Onion</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1 Can">Green Chiles</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1 Can">Cream of Mushroom Soup</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1/2 Cup">Sour Cream</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1 1/2 Cup">Chicken Breast</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1 Cup">Cheddar Cheese</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "Six">Flour Tortillas</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1/4 Cup">Milk</ingredient>
            <step>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Lightly grease a large baking dish.</step>
            <step>In a medium saucepan over medium heat, melt the butter and saute the green onion until tender (about 3 to 4 minutes). Add the garlic powder, then stir in the green chiles, cream of mushroom soup and sour cream. Mix well. Reserve 3/4 of this sauce and set aside. To the remaining 1/4 of the sauce in the saucepan, add the chicken and 1/2 cup of shredded Cheddar cheese. Stir together.</step>
            <step>Fill each flour tortilla with the chicken mixture and roll up. Place seam side down in the prepared baking dish.</step>
            <step>In a small bowl combine the reserved 3/4 of the sauce with the milk. Spoon this mixture over the rolled tortillas and top with the remaining 1/2 cup of shredded Cheddar cheese. Bake in the preheated oven for 30 to 35 minutes, or until cheese is bubbly.</step>
        </recipe>
    </lunch>
    <dinner>
        <recipe name = "Chicken Pot Pie" type = "Main Course" prep = "1 hour, 10 minutes">
            <description>Chicken, pot, and pie. My three favorite things all combined into one dish.</description>
            <ingredient amount = "1 Pound">Chicken breast</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1 Cup">Carrots</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1 Cup">Green peas</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1/3 Cup">Butter</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1/3 Cup">Onion</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1/3 Cup">All-purpose flour</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1/2 Teaspoon">Salt</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1/4 Teaspoon">Black pepper</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1/4 Teaspoon">Celery Seed</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "1 3/4 Cup">Chicken broth</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = "2/3 Cup">Milk</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount = '2 (9")' >Pie Crust</ingredient>
            <step>Preheat oven to 425 degrees F (220 degrees C.)</step>
            <step>In a saucepan, combine chicken, carrots, peas, and celery. Add water to cover and boil for 15 minutes. Remove from heat, drain and set aside.</step>
            <step>In the saucepan over medium heat, cook onions in butter until soft and translucent. Stir in flour, salt, pepper, and celery seed. Slowly stir in chicken broth and milk. Simmer over medium-low heat until thick. Remove from heat and set aside.</step>
            <step>Place the chicken mixture in bottom pie crust. Pour hot liquid mixture over. Cover with top crust, seal edges, and cut away excess dough. Make several small slits in the top to allow steam to escape.</step>
            <step>Bake in the preheated oven for 30 to 35 minutes, or until pastry is golden brown and filling is bubbly. Cool for 10 minutes before serving.</step>
        </recipe>
    </dinner>
</schedule>
<schedule date="5/13/2015" breakfast="Pumpkin Pancakes" lunch="" dinner="Chipotle Crusted Pork Tenderloin,Rosemary Mashed Potatoes and Yams" />
